<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Moder</string>
    <string name="profile_greeting">Hi <b>Joe!</b></string>
    <string name="ribbons_collected">Ribbons Collected: </string>
    <string name="cards_rated">Photos Rated: </string>
    <string name="title_activity_photo_edit">PhotoEditActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="register_now">Don\'t have an account? Register now !</string>
    <string name="register_now_u"><u>Don\'t have an account? Register now !</u></string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">RegistrationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms_of_service">TermsOfService</string>
    <string name="TOS">

<b>MODER TERMS AND CONDITIONS</b>
        \n


Credit

This document was created using a Contractology template available at http://www.freenetlaw.com.

Introduction

These terms and conditions govern your use of this mobile app, Moder; by using this app and clicking “accept”, you accept these terms and conditions in full.   If you disagree with these terms and conditions or any part of these terms and conditions, you must not use this mobile app.

You must be at least 13 years of age to use this mobile app.  By using this app [and by agreeing to these terms and conditions] you warrant and represent that you are at least 13 years of age.

This mobile app uses cookies.  By using this mobile app and agreeing to these terms and conditions, you consent to Moder\'s use of cookies in accordance with the terms of Moder\'s privacy policy.

License to use mobile app

Unless otherwise stated, Moder and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights in the mobile app and material on the mobile app.  Subject to the license below, all these intellectual property rights are reserved.

You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages or photos from the mobile app for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions set out below and elsewhere in these terms and conditions.

You must not:

republish material from this mobile app (including republication on another mobile app);
sell, rent or sub-license material from the mobile app;
show any material from the mobile app in public;
reproduce, duplicate, copy or otherwise exploit material on this mobile app for a commercial purpose;
edit or otherwise modify any material on the mobile app; or
redistribute material from this mobile app except for content specifically and expressly made available for redistribution.

Where content is specifically made available for redistribution, it may only be redistributed within Moder.

Acceptable use

You must not use this mobile app in any way that causes, or may cause, damage to the mobile app or impairment of the availability or accessibility of the mobile app; or in any way which is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity.

You must not use this mobile app to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software.

You must not conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to this mobile app without Moder\'s express written consent.

You must not use this mobile app to transmit or send unsolicited commercial communications.

You must not use this mobile app for any purposes related to marketing without Moder\'s express written consent.

You must not use this mobile app for harassment, intimidation, or bullying. Moder condones the expression of any overly sexual, inappropriate, or vulgar material.

You must not use this mobile app in a manner that violates others\' personal rights or violates the law.

Restricted access

Access to certain areas of this mobile app is restricted.  Moder reserves the right to restrict access to other areas of this mobile app, or indeed this entire mobile app, at Moder\'s discretion.

If Moder provides you with a user ID and password to enable you to access restricted areas of this mobile app or other content or services, you must ensure that the user ID and password are kept confidential.

Moder may disable your user ID and password in Moder\'s sole discretion without notice or explanation.

User content

In these terms and conditions, “your user content” means material (including without limitation text, images, audio material, video material and audio-visual material) that you submit to this mobile app, for whatever purpose.

You grant to Moder a worldwide, irrevocable, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute your user content in any existing or future media.  You also grant to Moder the right to sub-license these rights, and the right to bring an action for infringement of these rights.

Your user content must not be illegal or unlawful, must not infringe any third party\'s legal rights, and must not be capable of giving rise to legal action whether against you or Moder or a third party (in each case under any applicable law).

You must not submit any user content to the mobile app that is or has ever been the subject of any threatened or actual legal proceedings or other similar complaint.

Moder reserves the right to edit or remove any material submitted to this mobile app, or stored on Moder\'s servers, or hosted or published upon this mobile app.

Notwithstanding Moder\'s rights under these terms and conditions in relation to user content, Moder does not undertake to monitor the submission of such content to, or the publication of such content on, this mobile app.

No warranties

This mobile app is provided “as is” without any representations or warranties, express or implied.  Moder makes no representations or warranties in relation to this mobile app or the information and materials provided on this mobile app.

Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, Moder does not warrant that:

this mobile app will be constantly available, or available at all; or
the information on this mobile app is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading.

Nothing on this mobile app constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind. If you require advice in relation to any legal, financial or medical matter you should consult an appropriate professional.

Limitations of liability

Moder will not be liable to you (whether under the law of contact, the law of torts or otherwise) in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this mobile app:

to the extent that the mobile app is provided free-of-charge, for any direct loss;
for any indirect, special or consequential loss; or
for any business losses, loss of revenue, income, profits or anticipated savings, loss of contracts or business relationships, loss of reputation or goodwill, or loss or corruption of information or data.

These limitations of liability apply even if Moder has been expressly advised of the potential loss.

Exceptions

Nothing in this mobile app disclaimer will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit; and nothing in this mobile app disclaimer will exclude or limit Moder\'s liability in respect of any:

death or personal injury caused by Moder\'s negligence;
fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation on the part of Moder; or
matter which it would be illegal or unlawful for Moder to exclude or limit, or to attempt or purport to exclude or limit, its liability.

Reasonableness

By using this mobile app, you agree that the exclusions and limitations of liability set out in this mobile app disclaimer are reasonable.

If you do not think they are reasonable, you must not use this mobile app.

Other parties

You accept that, as a limited liability entity, Moder has an interest in limiting the personal liability of its officers and employees.  You agree that you will not bring any claim personally against Moder officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the mobile app.

Without prejudice to the foregoing paragraph, you agree that the limitations of warranties and liability set out in this mobile app disclaimer will protect Moder\'s officers, employees, agents, subsidiaries, successors, assigns and sub-contractors as well as Moder.

Unenforceable provisions

If any provision of this mobile app disclaimer is, or is found to be, unenforceable under applicable law, that will not affect the enforceability of the other provisions of this mobile app disclaimer.

Indemnity

You hereby indemnify Moder and undertake to keep Moder indemnified against any losses, damages, costs, liabilities and expenses (including without limitation legal expenses and any amounts paid by Moder to a third party in settlement of a claim or dispute on the advice of Moder\'s legal advisers) incurred or suffered by Moder arising out of any breach by you of any provision of these terms and conditions, or arising out of any claim that you have breached any provision of these terms and conditions.

Breaches of these terms and conditions

Without prejudice to Moder\'s other rights under these terms and conditions, if you breach these terms and conditions in any way, Moder may take such action as Moder deems appropriate to deal with the breach, including suspending your access to the mobile app, prohibiting you from accessing the mobile app, blocking phones using your MAC address from accessing the mobile app, contacting your wireless service provider to request that they block your access to the mobile app and/or bringing court proceedings against you.

Variation

Moder may revise these terms and conditions from time-to-time.  Revised terms and conditions will apply to the use of this mobile app from the date of the publication of the revised terms and conditions on this mobile app.  With any amendment to the terms and conditions or privacy policy, the user will be notified of the new versions and continued use of the mobile app will depend on acceptance of these new terms.

Copyright Complaints
Moder respects the ownership rights of its users. As a part of the Digital Millenium Copyright Act, Moder bears no responsibility for user content that violates copyright infringement. Still, Moder will work to disable or remove any proven infringing material.

To report a complaint, send an email to _____ with the subject of “copyright complaint”, containing a detailed description of the copyright material and the infringing material. It needs to contain sufficient detail that a reasonable decision can be made. Note that any user sending a complaint could potentially be held accountable for damages and fees incurred as a result of an incorrect characterization of copyright infringement.

If Moder determines content to be infringing, we will either disable and remove the content or alert the violating party. If the accused party pleads innocence, they may send an email to _____ with the subject of “copyright complaint counter notification” including sufficient details about their claim to make a reasonable decision. Note that any user sending a counter notification could potentially be held accountable for damages and fees incurred as a result of an incorrect characterization of copyright infringement. If Moder feels that it cannot make an appropriate decision, the case will be referred to courts.

If you are unsure whether a copyright violation has occurred, please consult an attorney or legal adviser.

Assignment

Moder may transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with Moder rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions without notifying you or obtaining your consent.

You may not transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with your rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions.

Severability

If a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect.  If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect.

Entire agreement

These terms and conditions, together with the Privacy Statment, constitute the entire agreement between you and Moder in relation to your use of this mobile app, and supersede all previous agreements in respect of your use of this mobile app.

Law and jurisdiction

These terms and conditions will be governed by and construed in accordance with Washington State Law, and any disputes relating to these terms and conditions will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Washington.

Registrations and authorisations

Moder is registered with Washington State.  You can find the online version of the register at http://www.sos.wa.gov/corps/search_detail.aspx?ubi=603459937.  Moder\'s UBI registration number is 603459937.

Moder\'s EIN number is 47-2544421.

Moder\'s details

The full name of Moder is Moder LLC.

Moder is registered in Washington under registration number  603459937.

You can contact Moder by email to contact@moderapp.com.
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    \n\n\n\n

    <p>
    <b>MODER PRIVACY STATEMENT</b>
    \n
Your privacy is important to Moder.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Moder collects, and the ways in which Moder uses that personal information.

Summary

This paragraph, which is in no way legally binding, highlights the main points of Moder\'s privacy statement. Like any digital service, Moder does collect user information in an attempt to better serve our users, match them with their interests, and improve the overall experience. Specifically:
Collected Information: registration user data (username, IP address, email, etc), user preferences, user publications (photos, etc)
Information Use: personalization of the mobile app, data analysis, marketing communications
Moder respects the privacy rights of its users and strives to keep information confidential and information use constructive and positive.

Credit

This document was created using a Contractology template available at http://www.freenetlaw.com.

Personal information collection

Moder may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

information about your use of this mobile app (including user interests/preferences, post/rating frequency, tag frequencies);
information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the mobile app (including username, email address, IP address, age(optional), and gender (optional));
information that you post publicly (including photos and outfit tags).

Using personal information

Moder may use your personal information to:

administer this mobile app;
personalize the mobile app for you;
enable your access to and use of the mobile app services;
publish information about you on the mobile app;
process data analysis;
send you marketing communications.

Where Moder discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Moder may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

Securing your data

Moder will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Moder will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers, which are owned by webhosting.com.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this mobile app will be  protected by encryption technology.

Cross-border data transfers

Information that Moder collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Moder operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the mobile app will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

Updating this statement

Moder may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this mobile app.

You will be alerted of changes to this privacy policy and acceptance of the new terms will be required for continued use of the mobile app.

Other mobile apps

This mobile app could contain links to other mobile apps.

Moder is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

Contact Moder

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Moder\'s treatment of your personal information, please write by email to contact@moderapp.com.
        By clicking below you agree to the terms and conditions of this document as well as the privacy policy.
    </p>

    </string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
